Guide to the Jack Anderson papers, 1930-2004 MS2001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Correspondence, 1960-1966; 1960-2004; MS2001 Series 5; 10 Linear Feet 20 document boxes
  - Reader correspondence, 1967
    - Reader correspondence [2 of 2], 1976; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - Reader correspondence [1 of 6], 1976; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - Reader correspondence [2 of 6], 1976; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Reader correspondence [3 of 6], 1976; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - Reader correspondence [4 of 6], 1976; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - Reader correspondence [5 of 6], 1977; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - Reader correspondence [6 of 6], 1977; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - Reader correspondence [1 of 11], 1977; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Reader correspondence [2 of 11], 1977; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - Reader correspondence [3 of 11], 1977; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - Reader correspondence [4 of 11], 1977; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - Reader correspondence [5 of 11], 1977; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - Reader correspondence [6 of 11], 1977; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Reader correspondence [7 of 11], 1977; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - Reader correspondence [8 of 11], 1977; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 241, Folder 3)
    - Reader correspondence [9 of 11], 1977; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 241, Folder 4)
    - Reader correspondence [10 of 11], 1978; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Reader correspondence [11 of 11], 1978; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Reader correspondence [1 of 11], 1978; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - Reader correspondence [2 of 11], 1978; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - Reader correspondence [3 of 11], 1978; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - Reader correspondence [4 of 11], 1978; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - Reader correspondence [5 of 11], 1978; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - Reader correspondence [6 of 11], 1978; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - Reader correspondence [7 of 11], 1978; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - Reader correspondence [8 of 11], 1978; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - Reader correspondence [9 of 11], 1978; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - Reader correspondence [10 of 11], 1979; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - Reader correspondence [11 of 11], 1979; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - Reader correspondence [1 of 4], 1979; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - Reader correspondence [2 of 4], 1979; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Reader correspondence [3 of 4], 1980; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - Reader correspondence [4 of 4], 1981; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - Reader correspondence, 1981; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - Reader correspondence [1 of 2], 1982; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 245, Folder 5)
    - Reader correspondence [2 of 2], 1983-1986; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 246, Folder 1)
    - Reader correspondence, 1987-1989; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - Reader correspondence, 1990-1994; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 246, Folder 3)
    - Reader correspondence, 1995-1999; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - Reader correspondence, 2000-2004; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - Reader correspondence, undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - Reader correspondence, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 247, Folder 2)
    - Reader correspondence, 1958-1965; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 438, Folder 1)
  - Research correspondence, 1960-1965
    - Research correspondence [1 of 2], 1966-1967; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Research correspondence [2 of 2], 1966-1969; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 427, Folder 1)
    - Research correspondence [1 of 2], 1970-1974; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 247, Folder 4)
    - Research correspondence [2 of 2], 1970-1974; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 427, Folder 2)
    - Research correspondence [1 of 2], 1975-1977; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - Research correspondence [2 of 2], 1975-1977; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 427, Folder 3)
    - Research correspondence [1 of 2], 1978-1979; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - Research correspondence [2 of 2], 1980-1984; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 427, Folder 4)
    - Research correspondence, 1980-1984; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 248, Folder 2)
    - Research correspondence [1 of 2], 1985-1989; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 248, Folder 3)
    - Research correspondence [2 of 2], 1985-1989; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 427, Folder 5)
    - Research correspondence [1 of 2], 1990-2003; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 248, Folder 4)
    - Research correspondence [2 of 2], 1991-2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 427, Folder 6)
    - Research correspondence, undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - Research correspondence, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 428, Folder 5)
    - Research correspondence, undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 438, Folder 3)
  - Other correspondence, undated
    This subseries contains some items that are restricted for 25 years from the date the collection was given to Gelman Library, in 2007. Gelman Library will open the materials beginning in 2032, which may involve having their security classifications reviewed by appropriate government agencies.
    - Business correspondence [1 of 3], undated; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 444, Folder 6)
    - Business correspondence [2 of 3], 1968-2004; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 444, Folder 7)
    - Business correspondence [3 of 3], 1966-1970; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 444, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Anderson books, 1971-1975; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with colleagues, 1976-1980; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 249, Folder 3, Box R1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with colleagues, 1981-1983; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 249, Folder 4, Box R1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with colleagues, 1984-1985; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 250, Folder 1, Box R1)
    - Correspondence with colleagues, 1986-1990; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 250, Folder 2, Box R1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with colleagues, 1991-1995; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with colleagues, 1996-2004; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box R1, Folder 2, Box 250, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence with colleagues, undated; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box R1, Folder 2, Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with colleagues, undated; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box R1, Folder 2, Box 250, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence with colleagues [1 of 2], 1967-1999; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box R1, Folder 2, Box 251, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with colleagues [2 of 2], 1969-1973; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 438, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with editors re: manuscripts, 1963-1980; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 251, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with newspaper editors, 1981-1990; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 459, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - invitations and thank you notes, 1991-2001; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 251, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - invitations and thank you notes, 1980-1995; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 251, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - invitations and thank you notes, undated; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 251, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - TV and film, undated; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 251, Folder 6)
    - Memos from staff [1 of 4], undated; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Memos from staff [2 of 4], undated; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - Memos from staff [3 of 4], 1941-1979; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Memos from staff [4 of 4], 1941-1979; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 438, Folder 2)
    - Personal/LDS correspondence [1 of 2], 1980-1989; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 251, Folder 7)
    - Personal/LDS correspondence [2 of 2], 1980-1989; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 251, Folder 8)
    - Personal/LDS correspondence [1 of 2], 1990-1999; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - Personal/LDS correspondence [2 of 2], 2000-2004; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - Personal/LDS correspondence, undated; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - Personal/LDS correspondence, 1969-1996; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - Personal/LDS correspondence, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 438, Folder 4)
- Television, radio, and film, undated; 1969-1996; MS2001 Series 6; 4 Linear Feet 8 document boxes
  This series contains scripts and proposals for television, radio, and film projects with which Anderson was associated. They date from 1969 to 1996 and are organized first by medium (e.g. television, radio, film), then by type of material (e.g. proposal, script, special) and then alphabetically by name. It does not contain audiovisual recordings; when available, they are in series 11.
  Anderson was a featured commentator on Good Morning America for nine years and hosted several television specials including Target: USA (1989) and Who Murdered JFK? (1988). Television programs for which scripts are available in this series include: Confessions of a Muckraker, Good Morning America, Inside Edition, Investigative Reports, The Muckrakers, Target USA, and Who Murdered JFK. They date from 1978 to 1996. There are also two folders containing scripts not labeled with a particular television program.
  Anderson also had a daily syndicated radio show on the Mutual Broadcasting Network. Radio programs for which scripts are available in this series include: American Family Hour, Jack Anderson Report, and Watch on Washington. They date from 1969 to 1993. Many commentaries begin with "This is Jack Anderson in Washington," so their folders have been labeled this way because it could not be determined which program they represented. There are also three folders containing scripts not labeled with a particular radio program.
  This series also contains several proposals and scripts for films with which Anderson was associated, some of which appear never to have been produced. Scripts are available for the following titles: The Anderson Project, Blood Feud, The Ten Plagues, and The Terrorist.
  This series has three subseries: Film, radio, and television.
  - Film, undated
    - BOA Productions- A Practical Approach to Independent Film Financing, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - Film, radio, and TV business, 1977; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - Film proposal - Inside Out, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - Film proposal - The Jack Anderson Story, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - Film proposal - Operation Mongoose, 1983; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 231, Folder 9)
    - Film proposal - Talons, 1978; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 231, Folder 10)
    - Film proposal - Yellow Rain, 1978; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Film script - The Anderson Project [1 of 2], 1983; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - Film script - The Anderson Project [2 of 2], undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 232, Folder 3)
    - Film script - Blood Feud, 1982; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - Film script - The Ten Plagues, Undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - Film script - The Terrorist, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - Radio, 1969-1993
    - Money Call scripts, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 436, Folder 3)
    - Radio scripts, undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 232, Folder 7)
    - Radio scripts, undated [1 of 2], Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 232, Folder 8)
    - Radio scripts, undated [2 of 2], Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Radio scripts - American Family Hour, undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Radio scripts - Commentary [1 of 2], undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Radio scripts - Commentary [2 of 2], undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Radio scripts - Jack Anderson Report [1 of 2], undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Radio scripts - Jack Anderson Report [2 of 2], undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Radio scripts - "This is Jack Anderson in Washington" [1 of 3], undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - Radio scripts - "This is Jack Anderson in Washington" [2 of 3], undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Radio scripts - "This is Jack Anderson in Washington" [3 of 3], Undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Radio scripts - Watch on Washington, undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - Television, undated
    - Anderson File promotional material, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 443, Folder 1)
    - The Anderson Papers TV proposal, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 436, Folder 1)
    - HBO pitch, 1975; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 436, Folder 2)
    - "Now It Can Be Told" TV proposal, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 436, Folder 4)
    - Scripts, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 436, Folder 5)
    - Special reports, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 436, Folder 6)
    - TV proposals [1 of 2], undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - TV proposals [2 of 2], undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 436, Folder 7)
    - TV proposal - The Capital Hills, 1978; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - TV proposal - Defend Yourself, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - TV proposal - Government As It Is, 1990; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - TV proposal - Jack Anderson Confidential, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - TV proposal - Now It Can Be Told, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - TV scripts [1 of 2], undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 234, Folder 10)
    - TV scripts [2 of 2], undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - TV scripts - Confessions of a Muckraker [1 of 2], undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - TV scripts - Confessions of a Muckraker [2 of 2], undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - TV scripts - Good Morning America [1 of 3], undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - TV scripts - Good Morning America [2 of 3], undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - TV scripts - Good Morning America [3 of 3], 1996; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - TV scripts - Inside Edition, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - TV script - Investigative Reports, 1989; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - TV script - The Muckrakers, 1989; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - TV special - Target USA [1 of 3], 1989; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - TV special - Target USA [2 of 3], 1988-1989; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - TV special - Target USA [3 of 3], undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 236, Folder 6)
    - TV special -- terrorism, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 436, Folder 8)
    - TV special - Who Murdered JFK?, 1951-1993; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 236, Folder 7)
    - USA Tomorrow, 1966; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 436, Folder 9)
- Business, charity, and legal, 1977; 1951-1993; MS2001 Series 7; 9.5 Linear Feet 19 document boxes
  This series contains correspondence, memos, reports, and legal documents relating to Jack Anderson's work with nonprofit advocacy groups, for-profit business interests, and legal cases to which he was a party. They date from 1951 to 2002 and are arranged alphabetically by organization/business name or by the name of a lawsuit.
  Not only a journalist, Anderson was also a crusader for causes close to his heart, founding and serving on boards of nonprofit advocacy groups promoting fiscal responsibility and educational reform. Anderson co-founded the think tank and advocacy group Citizens Against Government Waste with J. Peter Grace in 1984 in order to eliminate inefficiency and mismanagement in government. He also founded the Young Astronauts Council by persuading President Ronald Reagan in 1984 to charter an organization to motivate students to focus on math and science in school. In addition, he was among the founders of the Center for the School of the Future at Utah State University. Documents from all three organizations are included in this series, arranged first by the name of the organization and then by additional descriptors.
  Correspondence and memos relating to Anderson's business interests in this series include documents from companies and ventures in which he was a small shareholder as well as documents from publishers and publicists in Anderson's syndicated column and several newsletters. They are gathered together under the folder titles "Business dealings" but are not arranged in greater detail.
  The legal records in this series document several lawsuits to which Anderson and Drew Pearson were parties as part of their investigative work. In some cases they sued and in other cases were sued by the objects of their investigative reports. These lawsuits include: Anderson and Pearson v. Corso, Anderson v. Nixon, Carey v. Hume and Anderson, Curtis v. Anderson, Dodd v. Pearson and Anderson, Fite v. Anderson, Liberty Lobby v. Anderson, Littrell v. Pearson, Malaxa v. Pearson, Merrill and Kramer v. Anderson et al., O'Brien v. Anderson et al., Pearson v. McCarthy, and van Deerlin v. Anderson.
  - Anderson and Pearson v. Corso, Undated; Series 7 (Box 378, Folder 1)
  - Anderson v. Nixon, Undated; Series 7 (Box 443, Folder 2)
  - Business dealings [1 of 10], Undated; Series 7 (Box 378, Folder 2)
  - Business dealings [2 of 10], Undated; Series 7 (Box 378, Folder 3)
  - Business dealings [3 of 10], Undated; Series 7 (Box 378, Folder 4)
  - Business dealings [4 of 10], Undated; Series 7 (Box 378, Folder 5)
  - Business dealings [5 of 10], Undated; Series 7 (Box 379, Folder 1)
  - Business dealings [6 of 10], Undated; Series 7 (Box 379, Folder 2)
  - Business dealings [7 of 10], Undated; Series 7 (Box 379, Folder 3)
  - Business dealings [8 of 10], Undated; Series 7 (Box 379, Folder 4)
  - Business dealings [9 of 10], undated; Series 7 (Box 379, Folder 5)
  - Business dealings [10 of 10], undated; Series 7 (Box 379, Folder 6)
  - Business dealings, 1984; Series 7 (Box 440, Folder 4)
  - Business dealings, 1974-1976; Series 7 (Box 440, Folder 5)
  - Business dealings - Precision Computer Products, undated; Series 7 (Box 380, Folder 1)
  - Carey v. Hume and Anderson, undated; Series 7 (Box 380, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste -- general [1 of 3], undated; Series 7 (Box 440, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste -- general [2 of 3], 1995-2002; Series 7 (Box 440, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste -- general [3 of 3], 2003; Series 7 (Box 440, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - Board of Directors, 2004-2005; Series 7 (Box 380, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - Board of Directors, Undated; Series 7 (Box 380, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - Board of Directors, Undated; Series 7 (Box 380, Folder 5)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - correspondence [1 of 3], Undated; Series 7 (Box 381, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - correspondence [2 of 3], Undated; Series 7 (Box 381, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - correspondence [3 of 3], Undated; Series 7 (Box 381, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - documents and publications [1 of 3], Undated; Series 7 (Box 381, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - documents and publications [2 of 3], Undated; Series 7 (Box 381, Folder 5)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - documents and publications [3 of 3], Undated; Series 7 (Box 382, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - general [1 of 5], Undated; Series 7 (Box 382, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - general [2 of 5], Undated; Series 7 (Box 382, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - general [3 of 5], Undated; Series 7 (Box 382, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - general [4 of 5], Undated; Series 7 (Box 382, Folder 5)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - general [5 of 5], Undated; Series 7 (Box 382, Folder 6)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - marketing and promotion materials [1 of 2], Undated; Series 7 (Box 383, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - marketing and promotion materials [2 of 2], Undated; Series 7 (Box 383, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - Money Trackers, 2000; Series 7 (Box 383, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Against Government Waste - Trumps v. Bolduc, 1969; Series 7 (Box 383, Folder 4)
  - Concerned Citizens of Carderock and Jack Anderson v. Hubbard and Adat Shalom, Undated; Series 7 (Box 383, Folder 5)
  - Curtis v. Anderson, Undated; Series 7 (Box 383, Folder 6)
  - Depositions, Undated; Series 7 (Box 383, Folder 7)
  - Do the Write Thing [1 of 5], Undated; Series 7 (Box 383, Folder 8)
  - Do the Write Thing [2 of 5], Undated; Series 7 (Box 384, Folder 1)
  - Do the Write Thing [3 of 5], Undated; Series 7 (Box 384, Folder 2)
  - Do the Write Thing [4 of 5], 1968; Series 7 (Box 384, Folder 3)
  - Do the Write Thing [5 of 5], 1968; Series 7 (Box 384, Folder 4)
  - Dodd v. Pearson and Anderson, Undated; Series 7 (Box 450, Folder 4)
  - Dodd v. Pearson and Anderson -- Exhibits in the Boyd Deposition, 1985; Series 7 (Box 450, Folder 5)
  - Drew Pearson Foundation, 1971; Series 7 (Box 384, Folder 5)
  - Entertainment Industries Council, 1988; Series 7 (Box 384, Folder 6)
  - Fite v. Anderson, 1988; Series 7 (Box 385, Folder 1)
  - Freedom Package [1 of 5], 1988; Series 7 (Box 385, Folder 2)
  - Freedom Package [2 of 5], 1988; Series 7 (Box 385, Folder 3)
  - Freedom Package [3 of 5], 1988; Series 7 (Box 385, Folder 4)
  - Freedom Package [4 of 5], 1969; Series 7 (Box 385, Folder 5)
  - Freedom Package [5 of 5], Undated; Series 7 (Box 385, Folder 6)
  - Hicks' Pixies, Inc., Undated; Series 7 (Box 385, Folder 7)
  - International Platform Association, 1984; Series 7 (Box 385, Folder 8)
  - Legal - general, Undated; Series 7 (Box 385, Folder 9)
  - Liberty Lobby v. Anderson, 1956; Series 7 (Box 386, Folder 1)
  - Littrell v. Pearson, 1973-1974; Series 7 (Box 386, Folder 2)
  - Malaxa v. Pearson, 1972; Series 7 (Box 386, Folder 3)
  - Merrill and Kramer v. Anderson et al., 1972; Series 7 (Box 386, Folder 4)
  - O'Brien v. Anderson et al. [1 of 3], 1972; Series 7 (Box 386, Folder 5)
  - O'Brien v. Anderson et al. [2 of 3], Undated; Series 7 (Box 386, Folder 6)
  - O'Brien v. Anderson et al. [3 of 3], Undated; Series 7 (Box 386, Folder 7)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - clippings index, 1951; Series 7 (Box 387, Folder 1)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - Fulton, Lewis, 1951; Series 7 (Box 387, Folder 2)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - general [1 of 2], 1953; Series 7 (Box 387, Folder 3)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - general [2 of 2], 1951; Series 7 (Box 387, Folder 4)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - Matthews deposition, 1951; Series 7 (Box 387, Folder 5)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - McCarthy deposition [1 of 2], 1951; Series 7 (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - McCarthy deposition [2 of 2], 1953; Series 7 (Box 387, Folder 7)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - McCormick deposition, 1953; Series 7 (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - Pegler deposition [1 of 4], 1953; Series 7 (Box 388, Folder 2)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - Pegler deposition [2 of 4], 1953; Series 7 (Box 388, Folder 3)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - Pegler deposition [3 of 4], 1951; Series 7 (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Pearson v. McCarthy - Pegler deposition [4 of 4], 1951; Series 7 (Box 388, Folder 5)